const americaQuiz = [
    
    {
        question: "What is Bucky's real first and middle name?",
        choice1: "Brian Bucket",
        choice2: "James Buchanan",
        choice3: "Steve Rogers",
        choice4: "Robert Buchwald",
        answer: 2,
         },

     
        {
            question: "What is the name of the evil organization within the Third Reich?",
            choice1: "Hydra",
            choice2: "The Seven Sons",
            choice3: "Red Army",
            choice4: "Iron Fist",
            answer: 1,
        },

        {
            question: "Whats Captain America first name?",
            choice1: "Captain",
            choice2: "Robert",
            choice3: "Steve",
            choice4: "Jack",
            answer: 3,
        },

        {
            question: "What specific part of New York City is Steve Rogers from?",
            choice1: "Brooklyn",
            choice2: "Manhattan",
            choice3: "Staten Island",
            choice4: "Central Park",
            answer: 1,
        },


        {
            question: "What symbol is on Captain America's shield?",
            choice1: "Star",
            choice2: "Strips",
            choice3: "Dollar",
            choice4: "Squares",
            answer: 1,
        },


        {
            question: "In Avengers: Civil War, who does Captain America fight?",
            choice1: "Hulk",
            choice2: "Iron Man",
            choice3: "Vision",
            choice4: "Jarvis",
            answer: 2,
        },


        {
            question:"What is Captain America's shield made out of?",
            choice1: "Alloy Metal",
            choice2: "Titanium alloy",
            choice3: "Vibranium",
            choice4: "Wood",
            answer: 3,
        },


        {
            question:"Who is Captain America's best friend?",
            choice1: "Bucky",
            choice2: "Iron Man",
            choice3: "Thor",
            choice4: "Vision",
            answer: 1,
        },


        {
            question: "Who made Captain Americaâ€™s shield?",
            choice1: "Hydra",
            choice2: "Howard Stark",
            choice3: "Tony Stark",
            choice4: "Asgard",
            answer: 3,
        },


        {
            question: "What year was Steve Rogers born?",
            choice1: "1920",
            choice2: "1917",
            choice3: "1915",
            choice4: "1918",
            answer: 4,
        },


        {
            question: "What does Steve Rogers hate above all else by World War II?",
            choice1: "Man Kind",
            choice2: "Bullies",
            choice3: "Hydra",
            choice4: "War",
            answer: 2,
        },


        {
            question: "What is the Super Soldier Project officially known as?",
            choice1: "Super Soldier",
            choice2: "Project Rebirth",
            choice3: "Project Insight",
            choice4: "Project America",
            answer: 2,
        },

        {
            question: "What was Captain America's elite unit known as?",
            choice1: "Super Soldiers",
            choice2: "Howling Commandos",
            choice3: "Stars and Strips",
            choice4: "Team America",
            answer: 2,
        },

        {
            question: "What is Captain Americas love interest",
            choice1: "Peggy Carter",
            choice2: "Peggy Walsh",
            choice3: "Peggy Haris",
            choice4: "Peggy Wilson",
            answer: 1,
        },

        {
            question: "What does Steve promise Peggy before he gets frozen?",
            choice1: "Dancing",
            choice2: "Dinner",
            choice3: "Marriage",
            choice4: "Drive",
            answer: 1,
        },

        {
            question: "What year was Captain America unfrozen?",
            choice1: "2011",
            choice2: "2014",
            choice3: "2016",
            choice4: "2008",
            answer: 1,
        },

        {
            question: "Finish this Captain America quote: 'This isn't freedom.'",
            choice1: "This is America",
            choice2: "This is Robbery",
            choice3: "This is Fear",
            choice4: "This is Communism",
            answer: 3,
        },

        {
            question: "What was Captain America able to pick up in Endgame?",
            choice1: "Thanos",
            choice2: "A Bus",
            choice3: "A Car",
            choice4: "Thors Hammer",
            answer: 2,
        },

        {
            question: "Where Does Captain America crash the plane belong to Red Skull",
            choice1: "The Ocean",
            choice2: "The Artic",
            choice3: "The Desert",
            choice4: "Space",
            answer: 2,
        },

        {
            question: "It turns out that there is a secret Hydra base in which of these locations?",
            choice1: "The Mall of America",
            choice2: "Coney Island Boardwalk",
            choice3: "The White House",
            choice4: "Steve's old training base",
            answer: 4,
        },


 
]